♪♪
Well, thank you, Susan.
This is Brian Clayborn,
your entertainment editor,
coming to you live from
the new Rialto Theater,
where Nicky Tower
is due to arrive
virtually any second
now, for the premiere
of his new movie, which,
like many of his films, was
shot right here in Atlanta.
And, right now, I do believe
he is coming up
here, and... yes,
Nicky has arrived, as you
can tell from the crowd reaction.
Hey!
Hey, Atlanta, love you!
You're great!
You're the best!
We'll see if we can get a
word with him right now, Susan.
Get down!
Oh, my God!
Did you see that?
Someone on a motorcycle
just pulled up and
shot three shots
at Nicky Tower.
Nicky Tower is down.
Security guards
from the theater
are attending to him.
Uh, back to you, Susan and Bill.
Oh... No. No, no, no, no, no!
Get over!
Ben!
Well, Sherman.
How you doing?
Good to see you, Ben.
Boy, this is a switch.
Usually when we
run into each other
you're the one wearing the robe.
I need an attorney, Ben.
Uh... actually, my son does.
Well, why does he need a lawyer?
They think he killed someone.
He didn't.
Believe me, he'd
tell me if he had,
just to see the look on my face.
Oh, you didn't...
didn't, uh... get along.
That's an understatement.
Sandra and I were
divorced when he was nine.
I didn't see much of
him; I was very busy.
You know how it is.
I know I wasn't
much of a father.
This time, I'd like
to be there for him.
Well, did, uh, did
they arrest him yet?
He's in the lockup downtown.
Could you at least
talk to him, Ben?
Oh, well, y-yeah.
Yeah, I-I could do that.
I guess I better...
put on some britches.
All right, Sherman,
I'll put on...
them britches in there.
I'll be, uh...
So... you're Sherman
Lockwood's son.
That's right.
Who are you?
I'm a lawyer. Ben Matlock.
Oh, man.
My father didn't tell
you about me, did he?
Well, that's all right.
He's real good when it
comes to passing out judgment.
When it comes to telling
the truth, very mediocre.
No, he told me.
And he wants more than anything
to make up for past mistakes.
He's asked me to represent
you, and I'm willing to try.
Can you get me off?
I don't know.
I'm willing to try.
No promises. I'll try.
Yeah.
How are you at it?
- At what?
- Telling the truth.
Try me.
Why are you in here?
Somebody riding a bike
like mine killed Nicky Tower.
I used to work for him, so
the cops think it was me.
That's it?
Whoever did it used my gun.
Oh, you own a gun.
Yeah, I own a gun.
It's legal, it's registered.
Police found it?
Yeah, couple of blocks away
from where Nicky was killed.
You didn't like him?
I liked him fine
till he fired me.
Now the cops are
trying to make a big deal
out of this fight we had.
Fight?
Yeah, we had a fight.
He fired me for nothing, man.
When?
Day before the murder.
Mm.
Alibi?
I was riding my bike.
By yourself?
By myself!
Is that all right by you?!
You're in a lot of trouble,
and if you don't realize that,
you're in even more trouble.
Now, if you want
me to try to help you,
take that cigarette
out of your mouth,
put your feet down, sit up
and talk to me like a man,
and quit acting like a jackass!
Now, Ms. Williams,
you were Mr. Tower's
personal assistant for how long?
For eight years.
And were you in his
employ when he hired
the defendant, Cliff
Lockwood, to be his bodyguard?
- Yes, I was.
- How long ago was that?
That was two months ago,
right after Mr. Tower
arrived here in Atlanta
to begin prepping
for his new film.
Would you describe
for us the circumstances
under which the
defendant was hired?
Well, Nicky literally hired
him right off the street.
Probably got fake tattoos!
Hey, come on.
Come on, just one joke.
It's my birthday.
Listen, pal, I'm fresh
out of birthday jokes.
Well, a-any joke, then. Come on.
Excuse me, Mr. Tower
would just like to
go home, all right?
Hey, I paid $6.50 to
see your last movie,
and you know something?
It stank!
You owe me, Mr. Hollywood star.
Stay here.
Hey, hey, hey.
I got a joke for you.
Why'd the turkey cross the road?
Uh... I-I don't know.
Because he was about to get
the stuffing knocked out of him.
Hey.
Thanks, pal. That was great.
Did you ever think about
doing that for a living?
What, tell jokes?
I like this guy.
Hey, how'd you like
to be my bodyguard?
- Nicky...
- I'm serious... if people see
a biker, they're gonna run first
and ask questions later, right?
- Yeah, why don't, uh...
- Well, what do you think?
Want a job?
No.
I sure do need one.
Got a deal.
He hired him right on the spot
without even so much
as asking him his name.
Nicky loved doing
off-the-wall things like that.
Were you also present
when he fired the defendant?
Yes.
Would you describe that for us?
Well, Gary Benton,
the producer of the film
Nicky was going
to start shooting
here in town had arrived,
and they were going over some
set sketches in Nicky's room.
There aren't sets;
these are cages.
Who the hell designed these
things anyway, Jiminy Cricket?
Nicky! These are just sketches.
You'll love the
sets, believe me.
I'll tell you what I
believe... It's money again.
It's your damn chintzy budgets.
Why don't you just film
your stupid budget, all right?
Put that up on the screen,
see how many people come.
Nicky...
- I want to talk to you, Nicky.
- Cliff!
I just found out!
Cliff, get the hell in here!
You're gonna pay
for this, dirtbag!
Look, I don't know
what your problem is,
Miller, but you're this close
to being laid off, permanently!
Later, Nicky.
That guy's nuts!
Cliff!
Where is that slob?
Man, what's
happening? You call me?
Only about a hundred
times, you idiot.
- Where have you been?
- You sent me out
for hamburgers, remember?
That was hours ago!
There was a line.
You like waiting in line?
Why don't you try the line
at the unemployment office?
You're fired, bozo!
What goes around
comes around... bozo.
You happy?
How many times
prior to that incident
did Mr. Tower
express anger toward
or dissatisfaction
with my client?
- Well... uh, there...
- 12 times,
six times or none?
None that I'm aware of.
And during this
one isolated incident
that you described,
did my client
ever actually
threaten Mr. Tower?
Well... Did he?
Not in so many words, no.
Thank you.
So, Mr. Bonzer,
how many years have you
been selling motorcycles?
Opened my shop in 19-and-54.
Did you ever sell a
motorcycle to Mr. Lockwood?
Over the years,
I've sold him several.
What was the make and model
of the last bike you sold him?
Claymore 1200 Hyperglide.
Was it like this one?
Exactly like that one.
Are you sure about that?
The motorcycle he was
riding was identical to that one
in make and color, I'm positive.
How far from the Georgia
state border was Mr. Lockwood
when you pulled him over?
Less than ten miles.
Did he happen to mention
where he was going?
Said he was going cross-country.
Did he say he was on the
way out of the state of Georgia?
That's what he told
me; yes, ma'am.
Thank you.
No further questions.
Mr. Matlock, cross-examine?
Yes, sir. When you arrested
my client and told him
that, uh, Nicky Tower
had been murdered,
uh, how'd he react, surprised?
He seemed surprised, yes, sir.
How'd he act?
He didn't like it.
He, uh, was very agitated.
He used a lot of profanity.
Yeah. Well, when you
put the handcuffs on him,
how'd he react?
Well, he tried to resist,
but I had a hold on him.
Uh-huh. Did, did he
try to fight or run away?
Oh, I had a hold on him.
Just answer the question.
Did he try to fight or run away?
No, sir, he didn't do that.
Thank you.
The defendant will please rise.
Mr. Lockwood, I find that
sufficient evidence exists
to bind you over for trial
for the murder of
Nicholas Tower.
This matter will be set
for trial in Department 111
of the Superior Court
on the 11th of February.
This court is now in recess.
You got a light, hotshot?
Excuse me.
Now let me get this straight.
You say after your
argument with Nicky Tower,
you jumped on your bike
and you just started riding?
That's right.
That means you must
have been on the road
for close to 36 hours,
so somebody, somewhere,
had to have seen you...
Hopefully, at the
time of the murder.
What about waitresses?
No.
Motel clerks?
I ate out of vending machines
and I slept in the woods.
- Here.
- Great.
That stuntman Steve Miller,
why was he so mad
at Nicky that day?
No idea.
They get along?
Yeah, Steve supervised
the stunts on Nicky's
last three movies.
What about, what about
that, uh, producer, uh,
see what it says...
Yeah. Gary Benton.
They argued all the time.
About what?
I don't know, man.
Production stuff, I guess.
I was always in the other room.
I couldn't hear.
We're going to work.
The next time we
appear in court,
kinda clean
yourself up a little bit
and try to get some
different clothes, got it?
Yeah, I got it.
So why you are
representing the little creep?
Uh, it's, uh, it's personal.
So you were mad
at, uh... what was...?
- Nicky.
- Yeah.
Yeah, I was mad at
him. As a matter of fact,
if Gary and Renee
hadn't been there,
I'd probably
punched his lights out.
- How come?
- He lied to me.
He said that if I gaffed
four pictures for him,
he'd let me direct.
Then, after doing it,
found out he'd been pumping
sunshine up my you know what.
Is that why you weren't at
the premiere that next night?
How do you know I wasn't there?
Well, your-your name
was on the guest list,
but you never
picked up your ticket.
Well, last thing I
wanted to do was look
at that little geek
for two hours.
Mm.
So, uh... what did you do?
I stayed at home.
You got a family?
I'm divorced.
Oh. So you were,
you were by yourself.
That night I was, yeah.
Huh.
Does that hurt?
Use it or lose it.
Yeah.
Careful over there!
Looks like you lost it.
Yeah.
Yeah, you lose it in my line
of work, and you're history.
Speaking of history,
I hear you did all that
incredible motorcycle stunt work
in Daredevil's Alley.
Yeah, that was me.
I don't do bike work anymore.
- It's too dangerous.
- Yeah.
Yeah, I imagine it is.
Yeah, I guess...
Yeah, I guess would be.
Yeah, that...
Around the side there.
Look, the star is dead,
so the picture's dead.
What can I tell you?
Call my secretary when
you get back to L.A.
We'll do lunch, okay?
Yeah, all right, ciao. Ciao.
Jackie! Yo, Jack.
You want to tell your
guys that the picture's over?
No goldbricking!
I said no overtime
and I mean it!
- Come on.
- Mr. Benton?
Who are you?
Conrad McMasters.
I'm a private investigator.
I'm not interested.
Excuse me?
PI's are box office poison.
Try one of the networks.
I work for Ben Matlock,
Cliff Lockwood's attorney.
I need to ask you some
questions if I could, please.
Oh!
I'm sorry.
People are always
coming up to me and trying
to sell me the rights
to their life story:
cops, doctors, teachers,
lawyers, dentists.
Uh, I understand that you and
Nicky Tower used to argue a lot.
We argued constantly!
I'd budget something at
$20,000, he had to have $40,000.
I'd get him the $40,000,
suddenly he needed $80,000.
It was one continuous battle.
So, it wasn't, it wasn't
anything personal?
No, no, no, of course not.
No, Nicky and I... all things
considered... we got on famously.
So then why didn't you go to
the premiere of his new movie?
'Cause it wasn't my movie.
I was only here to
prep my new picture.
And what'd you do that night?
Uh, I ate dinner at the hotel,
made some calls, read the
trades; you know, the usual.
Well, thank you for your time.
Sure.
Representing Cliff
Lockwood, huh?
I don't get it.
Hey, you know, actually,
actually, a lot of the
experiences I've had
would make a pretty good movie.
If I could leave another...
Ah! Buh-buh-bye-bye.
Yeah. I'm sorry.
Of course he was
difficult; he was a star.
And stars aren't necessarily
on the same wavelength
as the rest of us.
That's what makes them special.
Yeah, I hear he ran you ragged.
Here you go.
That was my job. I didn't mind.
Did you, did you know
that he... he
promised Steve Miller
a shot at a picture?
Who told you that?
Steve Miller.
Nicky never did any such thing.
I said he was
special, not stupid.
I thought you said he
liked to do the unexpected.
If you're trying to pin his
murder on Steve Miller,
that is fine with me.
I think the guy's
a first-class leech,
but we both know
your client killed Nicky.
He's a bum,
Mr. Matlock, a loser.
Back in my wilder days, I
had a boyfriend just like him.
He was a biker.
All he wanted to do
was ride his motorcycles
and hang out with his buddies.
He was lazy and shiftless
and violent, just like Cliff.
I tried to warn Nicky, but
he wouldn't listen to me.
Is this you?
Yes.
I, uh, I went into the theater
to make some last-minute
seating changes
when I heard the shots.
Actually, I didn't even know
that they were shots until...
I came out a couple of minutes
later and I... I saw a body
lying on the ground.
When I saw that it was Nicky...
I loved him, in case
you hadn't guessed.
Hey.
Got your message.
What's up?
Well, I don't know.
Nobody I've talked
to has anything nice
to say about our boy Cliff.
Yeah, me, too.
The call him bum, creep.
One of 'em said right
out that he killed this, uh...
- Nicky.
- Yeah, yeah.
But this Steve Miller lied about
the argument he had with Nicky
the day before the murder.
His alibi isn't
very good either.
So what are you
doing, following him?
You don't think
it's a good idea?
Yeah, okay, I'll take over.
Where's he at, in
the bar over there?
No, he's in the shop next to it.
You gotta be kidding.
No, wait! Ben, don't!
No, Ben, no, no! Let
me drive, all right?
Let me drive.
- He's-He's-He's pulling out!
- Wait!
Ben, you're not very
good at this. Don't!
Who's that?
- Ben, you're too close.
- No, I'm not.
Yes, you are. He's
gonna see you.
No, he won't.
He ju... He just did!
I don't believe this!
Oh!
You following me?
Just want to ask you a
couple more questions.
No way! Get out of here!
Don't... don't I know
you from somewhere?
Get back inside. Hurry up.
No, wait. Didn't I see
you at the courthouse?
Vicky, I said go back inside!
You were at Cliff Lockwood's
hearing, weren't you?
Were... STEVE: Damn it!
I'm sorry, Daddy, I had to go.
I had to see the
man who killed Nicky.
This is your daughter?
Why don't you just get lost?
You knew Nicky?
Hey, you don't
have to answer him.
Would you rather I subpoena her
and have her
answer in open court?
I was in love with him.
He's the father.
Why don't you...
uh, go inside, and we'll
see how that new blouse fits.
At first, she told me that it
was, uh, a boy from her school.
And then when I
found out the truth,
I wanted to kill
the little letch.
But I didn't do it.
I was here visiting
Vicky when he got shot.
Oh, why don't you ask her.
It's her grandmother's house.
Hi.
Me and the homeboys are
gonna take a little road trip.
Just wanted to say good-bye.
When you coming back?
I'm not.
I don't stand a
snowball's chance in hell
in that courtroom,
and you know it.
You don't stand a
snowball's chance in hell
if you leave.
Well, thanks to you and
my old man for all your help.
He and your justice system
are perfect for each other.
I gotta tell you something.
I don't give a merry
damn what you do.
Good.
You leave... you got no chance!
You stay, you
might have a chance.
A chance at what,
going to prison?
That ain't gonna happen.
Good riddance.
He just took off?
Like a bat out of hell,
as the saying goes.
You talk to his father?
Yep.
He said if I dropped the
case, he'd understand.
Are you going to?
Oh, yeah.
But if you drop the case,
he's gonna go through
the rest of his life
thinking he was right.
About his father,
about the system...
about you.
Well...
Oh... Haven't you
ever been wild?
No, not much.
Mama wouldn't let me.
I'm glad.
Well, I have.
I used to get drunked up, fight.
I had a bike.
Jail?
Yeah.
Fight and disorderly.
What turned you around?
My father told me if I didn't
stop my troublemaking,
I was gonna wind up in
a place worse than hell.
He told me he loved me,
he cared about me... Yeah?
Yeah, then he hit me right
here as hard as he could.
And then what?
I saw... the man knew
what he was talking about.
Yeah.
So what are you gonna do?
I don't know.
Don't know.
Case is only a
couple of days away.
Could be in Mexico, Ben.
Yeah.
Well... maybe you
better get going.
Oh, oh, oh.
By the way, Gary Benton wasn't
in his motel room the
night of the murder.
A parking attendant
remembers bringing his car up
at 5:30 and then parking it
for him an hour or so later.
Huh.
You know where he went?
You got a motive?
The word is that the film
that Gary was prepping
was a surefire bomb.
Evidently, Nicky Tower took
a script that everyone loved
and then rewrote it until
it was a piece of garbage.
You think that's what all the
arguments were really about?
Uh-huh. According to the
crew, this film was so bad
that if it had been released,
it would've destroyed
Gary's career.
Well, I'll be dogged.
Huh.
We'll have to keep
that one in mind.
I'll see you.
Yeah...
You know, you're right.
I don't think I was in my hotel.
Oh, I was out getting dinner.
Where?
Uh, I don't remember right off.
I go to a lot of places.
You know, I'm still looking for a
decent restaurant around here.
Oh.
I can't wait till this
trial thing is over,
so I can get back to L.A.
Yeah.
Uh...
what-what, uh, what
happened to the, uh, movie
you came here to produce?
Defunct.
It was tailor-made
for Nicky Tower.
With him gone,
studios aren't interested.
I hear it was
gonna be a stinker.
W-Well...
well, it wasn't gonna win
any Oscars, that's for sure.
But, uh...
But it worked out
for the best, didn't it?
I mean, the studio
had Nicky insured
and you're out from under
a project that might have
made you a laughingstock
back in, uh, Hollywood.
Ida Clayton, please
pick up the house phone.
Nicky Tower may have been
a pain in the neck, Mr. Matlock,
but he was a friend of mine.
And his death was
a great loss to me.
In fact, I shouldn't be talking
to anybody but my shrink,
so if-if you don't mind, I'd...
W-Well, wait a minute,
wait a minute, wait a minute.
I-I found a biographical
sketch on you in the library.
Uh-huh.
Did you know that you're in
Who's Who in the Film Industry?
Of course I am.
And-and-and the sketch said that
one of your hobbies
is racing motorcycles.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Well, the guy that does my
publicity tends to exaggerate.
I don't race them, I ride them.
- Uh-huh...
- Occasionally.
And only the little ones.
The success motivation seminar
will be taking place at
7:00 p.m. tonight
in the Empire Room.
The seminar is
open to the public,
and details are available
at the concierge desk.
Why don't we ask
that girl to join us?
What do you mean?
That girl.
Hi!
I'd rather not.
You want me to talk
with her by myself?
You want to know where I
was when Nicky was murdered?
I was with her.
She was upset.
You see, Nicky...
got a little kinky.
H-How upset was she?
She said she was
going to sell her story
to the National Informer.
Ooh. Ooh.
So you paid her off, huh?
Look, you're not,
you're not gonna
tell anybody
about this, are you?
I mean, the public adored Nicky.
People would be
devastated if they found out.
And it wouldn't
exactly do wonders
for my reputation either.
I-I don't understand something.
Why didn't you just quit?
Because they were
paying me $875,000
plus two percent of the gross.
Oh.
Ben, it's me.
Hi. Any luck?
Yeah. I'm in a bar
on Highway 53
just south of Griffin
called The Corral.
Cliff and his pals are inside.
Don't let him leave.
What do you mean
don't let him leave?
Hello?
It's all yours.
Who's going with me now?
Huh? Oh, baby.
Who's coming with me?
That guy, uh, right there...
All right.
Give them up.
What are you talking about?
My plug wires, that's
what I'm talking about!
- I don't have them.
- Where are they?
- What are you talking about?
- Get him, Sonny.
Get him out of there.
Quick, get him out of there.
You don't mess with a
man's bike, you hear me?!
You don't mess
with a man's bike!
Think about it, man!
If I find you, so will the cops!
Oh, yeah?
Teach you not to
mess with a man's bike.
Look out.
Get out of the way!
Well, look who's here.
Easy, easy.
- Watch it!
- Hey!
Watch it!
Get in the car.
I'm not going
nowhere with you, man.
Either you go
with me in that car
or you go to prison
with the cops in theirs.
That courtroom crap of yours
doesn't work for people like me.
Get in the car!
You just leave me alone.
Quit acting stupid
and get in the car!
Stupid?
Yeah, stupid!
You're getting
back at your father
and everything he
represents... Law, reason.
That's your problem.
Whether you killed
that fella or not,
unless you face trial, you're
going to prison surer than hell.
I don't know what you call
that, but I call that stupid!
How do I know
you can get me off?
You don't.
But I'm the only shot
you got right now.
Get in the car.
Get in the car!
Right now, I do believe
Nicky has arrived!
As you can tell from
the crowd reaction.
People taking pictures
for their photo albums.
- Here you go.
- We're gonna see
if we can get a word
with Nicky right now.
If we can get in here...
Ben.
- In here.
- Oh, my God,
did you see that?
Someone just rode by
- on a motorcycle...
- Hey.
How about a nice, fresh
piece of hot apple pie?
Oh, great!
Thanks.
How'd you know I'd still be up?
The trial's in two days; you
don't know who the killer is...
I knew you'd be up.
I got a notion.
Just a notion?
Well, it's pretty good though.
Are you gonna tell me?
- What?
- What the notion is.
Oh, my God!
Look at that.
Get in here.
Why didn't I see that before?
We've still got two days.
Huh. Great.
Yeah.
All right, man, how do I look?
You look like a winner.
Well?
Yes, that's right.
I sold him a bike
just like that one.
A Claymore 1200 Hyperglide.
Thank you, Mr. Bonzer.
Your witness.
Uh, Mr. Bonzer...
I'm going to show you
something, uh, which we'll identify
as Defense Exhibit K,
and which the
prosecution has stipulated
belongs to my client.
His Claymore 1200
Hyperglide motorcycle.
Yeah!
Objection!
- What?
- Objection!
Mr. Matlock!
Have him turn that thing off!
Hey, Chester! Turn it off!
Your Honor,
I object... to these
cheap theatrics.
Well, you said I could
bring the motorcycle
in the courtroom.
I said bring it
in, not ride it in!
Your Honor, I... I
apologize for-for the noise,
but I-I had to do it in order
to get my next point across.
All right.
Proceed.
Oh, thank you.
Now, Mr., Mr. Bonzer,
why is this bike so noisy?
You got dual exhaust.
Dual exhaust. D... Oh. Yes.
Two exhausts.
There's one right
here and one right here.
Yeah. Yeah, two.
Now...
how-how... that's the bike
the murderer was riding.
How many...
how many exhaust pipes
on... on that motorcycle?
I can't tell from that angle.
Uh-huh. Okay, how about here?
Fast-forward, yeah.
That angle.
- Single exhaust.
In other words, the bike
my client owns is not the bike
the person who shot Nicky
Tower is riding after all, is it?
Nope, it sure isn't.
Thank you.
Cross?
Mr. Bonzer, isn't it
possible that Mr. Lockwood
could have installed those
dual pipes after the murder?
- Nope.
- Why not?
'Cause I installed
them pipes myself
a good six weeks
before the murder.
Oh.
The prosecution
rests, Your Honor.
Mr. Matlock, call
your first witness.
Uh, defense calls Ms.
Renee Williams to the stand.
You may be seated.
Uh, wh-when you learned
that my client didn't have
any liability insurance,
you insisted that he
get some, didn't you?
Yes. Well, he wasn't exactly
what I would call a
responsible citizen.
I didn't want Mr. Tower
to wind up getting sued
for an accident which
- your client had caused.
- Mm-hmm.
Who paid for the policy?
Mr. Tower did.
Who did the actual paperwork?
I did. Handling his
financial matters
- was part of my job.
- Mm-hmm.
My client had to describe
his motorcycle in every detail
on that insurance form
application, didn't he?
- I believe so, yes.
- Yeah.
You took...
that description to a
shop down in Macon
the day before the murder
so you could rent a bike
exactly like his, didn't you?
I did no such thing, no.
Of course, you didn't use
your real name, you paid cash,
wore big sunglasses and
a red wig, but that was you
that rented a Claymore
1200 Hyperglide motorcycle
from Rory's Motorcycle
Shop on the 19th,
and returned it on the
21st, wasn't it, Ms. Williams?
- No, it wasn't.
- Course...
course there's...
one-one thing happened.
My client put those dual
exhausts on after he filled out
the application form.
See, that's unfortunately
a little detail you missed.
I have no idea what
you're talking about.
You insisted he register
all his firearms, didn't you?
Yes.
So you knew he had a gun.
Well, yes, but...
You could've stolen that
gun, shot Nicky Tower with it,
and everybody would
think my client had done it.
- That is not true.
- Objection!
This is pure speculation.
Mr. Matlock has yet
to prove any of this.
Sustained. Mr. Matlock,
I strongly suggest
you move on with
another line of questioning.
Uh, yes, sir. Boy, that's
a beautiful bracelet.
Ooh, look at that.
Whew!
Nicky Tower gave
you that, didn't he?
Yes, he did.
And-and-and on the underside,
there's an inscription, says...
says: "T-To my only love,
with love forever. Nicky."
Right?
- Yes, there-there is.
- Yeah.
There is.
He gave a bracelet just
like that to somebody else.
And we traced it to a
jeweler in Los Angeles.
Nicky Tower bought
not one, not two, but
12 of those bracelets.
You were in love
with him, weren't you?
Yes, I was.
My client overheard
the fight you had with him
when the bill for
those bracelets
accidentally came
across your desk.
You were furious, weren't you?
And when you heard
the two of them fighting...
My client and Nicky Tower...
You rented that
motorcycle, stole his gun,
waited in the alley the
night of the premiere
until the right moment,
then roared by
on that motorcycle,
shot Nicky Tower
three times, rode it into
the back of a waiting
van parked in a garage,
changed as quickly as possible,
got back down to the
street, over the body,
so you could have your
picture in the paper, all...
- for revenge.
- No!
Your Honor, Your
Honor, he's doing it again.
Mr. Matlock seems incapable
of telling the difference
between conjecture and proof.
I-I have proof, Your Honor.
Overruled.
There were, uh, a
lot of photographers
taking a lot of
pictures that night.
Among them... Robby
Atkins, there in the front row.
See? There he is on the screen.
He was trying out a...
a new telephoto camera
his uncle had given him.
And... according to these...
This is... This here
is-is... blowups...
of one of those pictures.
Pass those around.
There you go, sir.
And as you can see...
that lens did beautifully.
I mean, even in blowup here,
the image is razor-sharp.
It is so sharp...
that you can see the reflection
in-in the window in the
building across the street
of a person sitting
astride a motorcycle
in the alley next
to the theater.
It's the killer...
just before she
puts... her helmet on.
Look here. Look, look.
You can even see
the gun in her hand.
See it there, right
by the helmet?
That is you... isn't
it, Ms. Williams?
Your Honor, in view
of these developments,
the prosecution
moves to dismiss.
I can't believe it,
man... You got me off.
Innocent people are
supposed to get off.
Cliff?
Congratulations.
Thanks.
Ben, thank you.
I don't know how I
ever can repay you.
Well, why don't you and Cliff
go somewhere and talk it over?
Something... new and
good might come of it.
Anywhere you want to go.
Maybe we could talk.
Sure, okay.
Thanks, dude.
Hey, where's he going, man?
We gotta celebrate.
Uh, he's gonna celebrate.
What do you say, Matlock?
Need a lift?
www.tvsubtitles.net